[wind howling]
Arise.
[rumbling]
[roaring]
Good.
♪
[BAEK YOONHO]
How long has it been?
[AHN SANGMIN]
About three hours.
Which would mean three days
have passed on the other side.
And red gates are supposed
to be especially brutal.
[yawns]
Welp, it's fair to assume
this punk's as good as dead.
What a huge waste of time.
♪
[HWANG DONGSOO]
Oh, and just to be clear...
Jinwoo Sung isn't with
the White Tiger Guild, right?
So, I gotta wonder
what business he has
with your strike team
if he's unaffiliated with you.
[sighs]
♪
Hunter Sung
is an acquaintance of mine,
he wanted to observe
a C-Rank raid,
so I brought him in.
[Hwang Dongsoo scoffs]
Is that all?
[footfall]
[sighs]
[grunting]
[HWANG DONGSOO]
Do I really seem that gullible?
Just what have you
dug up this time?
[grunting]
You've always had
a knack for sniffing out
hunters of interest,
so what makes an E-Rank--
[gasps]
[BAEK YOONHO]
Dongsoo Hwang.
Take your filthy hands
off of him.
D'you think that you
can order me around?
[HWANG DONGSOO]
You're just a big fish
in a tiny pond of a country.
♪
[BAEK YOONHO]
Say that again.
[trembling]
This is bad!
If they aren't stopped soon,
we'll have an S-Rank battle
on our hands!
[HWANG DONGSOO]
You wanna go?
[crackling]
[trembling]
[growling]
[thud]
[rumbling]
[Kim Chul shivering]
It was way too cold.
Yeah, we didn't have
the right gear with us.
That's... that's why we lost.
[gasps]
I was wondering
where all the bears went!
Did those E-Ranks do this?
[panting]
No, those weaklings
could never!
[trembling]
I forgot, the Slayers.
They're coming!
Shit!
[scoffs]
[wind gusting]
[crackling]
I'm almost impressed.
It'd be less impressive...
if you hadn't held back
at the last second.
My arms surely
would've been blown off.
[Woo Jinchul sighs]
[WOO JINCHUL] While I don't
know what his significance
is to you, Hunter Hwang,
I will at least say this...
I was able to re-evaluate
Hunter Sung two months ago.
He was an E-Rank then,
and he's an E-Rank now.
The Surveillance Team declared
your brother's cause of death
as KIA while fighting
a magic beast.
Right, perfect way
to silence public inquiry.
[HWANG DONGSOO]
And laughably fake.
The real killer's gotta be
that rich little turd
from Yoojin Construction.
If that's what you believe,
I'm confused
as to why you're after Sung.
It isn't obvious?
I wanna spill some blood...
and I've got a great excuse.
[phone vibrating]
Hm?
[scoffs]
The bastard lucked out.
[footfall]
-[running footsteps]
-[WOO JINCHUL] W-wait a moment!
[AHN SANGMIN] None of them
understand Hunter Sung's power,
but I do.
[engine whirring]
He'll definitely
walk out of this gate alive.
[GO MYUNGHWAN]
And then I realized,
I had no money left
to buy gear!
-[PARK HEEJIN] What?
-[Han Song-Yi chuckles]
[GO MYUNGHWAN] It was horrible!
My math was all wrong.
That's just
how expensive it was!
[KIM CHUL]
What the hell?
How are they even alive?
With winter coats, blankets,
a tent, and... and food!
Oh, I get it now.
-[laughing]
-[KIM CHUL] Hey!
-[PARK HEEJIN] Captain?
-[growling]
My team was wiped out
'cause we didn't have
the right gear or supplies!
While, you're out here
enjoying a damn cookout?
Hey, calm down.
[KIM CHUL] Which one
of you is the hoarder?
Who was keeping
all of this a secret?
You got my teammates killed!
Heejin Park.
[HAN SONG-YI]
I'm scared!
[KIM CHUL] You knew...
from the get-go.
That's why you went with them.
I'll consider everyone guilty
if you don't answer!
So, somebody'd better talk
by the count of three!
One!
Two!
Whether they confess or not...
I know it was Sung!
Three!
-[SUNG JINWOO] Four.
-[Kim Chul grunts]
[Kim Chul screams]
You're blaming your comrades'
deaths on who, exactly?
[HAN SONG-YI] Mister!
[GO MYUNGHWAN] Great timing!
[SUNG JINWOO] I also see
you brought unwanted guests.
Drop the Stealth.
You can't completely mask auras
that strong, anyway.
[PARK HEEJIN]
Are those ice elves?
[chuckles]
Yeah, it's a whole
platoon of 'em!
Along with the boss.
[thuds]
♪
This is quite
the surprise, indeed.
It appears even scum
can be competent.
How ironic,
calling human beings "scum"
when you elves
are the ruthless killers.
[speaking foreign language]
[BARCA] Well, more
competent than I thought!
Interesting.
You actually speak
our language, do you?
[Sung Jinwoo gasps]
But why do I speak it?
That's nuts.
You're having a whole
conversation with that guy.
[SUNG JINWOO]
This is the system's doing.
I'll make this simple
since you understand me.
Allow me
to reintroduce my friend.
[BARCA] He told me there was
a strong one among your group.
He wants to challenge you
in a battle and--
[blood splashing]
And?
[Barca chuckles]
You amuse me.
♪
[swords clanging]
[SUNG JINWOO]
He's not gonna be easy.
This keeps getting better.
I have to ask, though.
Why mingle with humans
and pretend to be one
when you're obviously not?
-What?
-[Barca chuckles]
[BARCA]
Considering your reaction,
I suppose you aren't aware?
We can hear a voice
inside our heads.
Always saying, "kill humans",
but, there's no
such instruction
when it comes to you.
[SUNG JINWOO]
A voice giving orders?
Kind of like
the system directives.
If the voice isn't
pitting them against me,
I can only assume
it's because I'm the Player.
Surely you'll agree that
we've no need to fight.
So, let's handle this sensibly,
shall we?
Give us the humans
who're cowering behind you.
[BARCA] Once you do,
we'll leave you be and depart.
Well?
What say you to our offer?
I say tell me who you guys are.
[SUNG JINWOO]
And why you're fighting humans.
In truth, we are...
[static buzzing]
Give us the humans
who're cowering behind you.
[BARCA] Once you do,
we'll leave you be and depart.
[SUNG JINWOO]
What was that just now?
Well?
What say you to our offer?
Do we have an agreement, or no?
♪
[chuckles]
No, we don't.
You honestly intend to make
enemies of us instead?
We clearly outnumber you...
if you haven't noticed.
[Sung Jinwoo chuckles]
Sure about that?
[roaring]
[gasps]
What's happening?
Um, are these knights
and bears on our side,
or is that wishful thinking?
They're made of shadow.
Every single one of them.
And Hunter Sung...
must be their master.
What an outrageous
waste of time.
Oh, you think so?
Stick around and find out.
[chuckles]
Ugh.
♪
[screaming]
[growling]
[swords clanging]
♪
Ya!
[arrow thwacks]
-[roars]
-Ah!
Get out of their way!
I don't think any of us will be
much help in this fight!
[panting]
♪
[arrow thwacks]
[thuds]
[SUNG JINWOO]
I see why he was so confident.
Though my summons are immortal,
they can't respawn
without mana.
I have a lot,
but it's bound to run out.
Then there's the boss.
I can tell
he's stronger than me.
Aa!
[thumping]
♪
[BARCA]
Ah!
[SUNG JINWOO]
This'll be a challenge,
even with Igris.
My regular soldiers
won't cut it.
I need something more powerful.
I am called Barca,
might I have your name as well?
♪
[crackling]
I'm Jinwoo Sung.
♪
[wind howling]
[chuckling]
[growls]
♪
[metal clanging]
[growling]
[gasps]
♪
[growls]
[grunts]
♪
It's been ages since I've
enjoyed a fight this much.
[sighs]
Hu?
[gasps]
[fire crackling]
[explosion]
♪
[groaning]
What the heck was I hit by?
♪
[grunting]
You're gonna pay!
♪
[SUNG JINWOO]
My mages bought me some time.
Now, then.
You're in trouble if that's
the best your soldiers can do!
Jinwoo Sung!
You die!
[BARCA]
Even the humans want you dead!
♪
[scoffs]
Futile!
[BARCA]
You cannot hide from me!
[roaring]
Jinwoo Sung!
You die!
Captain Kim.
I knew I could count on you.
[wind gusting]
[thuds]
[scoffs]
Futile!
[gagging]
[Kim Chul gasps]
You dirty... bastard!
Somehow you knew...
this would happen,
from the start.
Damn it all!
♪
[SUNG JINWOO]
Arise.
♪
You cannot hide from me!
[roaring]
[grunts]
[scoffs]
[sword clanking]
[growls]
[SUNG JINWOO]
From now on...
your name is Iron.
You understand?
♪
[grunting]
[roaring]
You truly are most amusing!
But your new toy won't
be as much fun in pieces!
♪
[explosion]
[chuckles]
A lumbering giant
with no agility!
♪
Just wondering, but would you
call this the standard?
As far as hunter battles go,
I mean.
[PARK HEEJIN] If it was,
do you think I would've
chosen this career?
I've never seen
a fight like this.
It's real?
We're sure
it's not an illusion?
[thudding]
[BARCA] This one
leaves me wanting more.
Stiffen your spine
and get over here!
Bring your knight
with you, too!
[chuckles]
On our way.
[grunts]
[swords clanging]
[BARCA]
Ya!
Ya! Ha!
[roaring]
[BARCA] All right.
Hu! You die first!
[growls]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[gagging]
[SUNG JINWOO] He dodged
a fatal blow after all that?
Persistent as ever,
but I suggest you quit
taking me lightly.
You're definitely strong,
I admit.
But, hey...
least your strength
in numbers is gone.
Ha?
Ah?
[gagging]
[trembling]
Very well.
Let's see what your rabble
amounts to without you!
♪
Throwing away
your weapon like a fool?
♪
[gasps]
[grunts]
[groaning]
Iron, now!
[roaring]
[grunting]
♪
[growling]
[explosion]
♪
[sword slashing]
How dare you
disrespect me this way?
I am going to slaughter
all of you!
♪
Looks like it's over.
[BARCA]
Don't give me that!
It's over when I say...
[crackling]
[gasps]
[screams]
[blood splatters]
♪
[SUNG JINWOO]
I said...
it's over.
♪
[sighs]
He was tough, but I did it.
[thumping]
Oh, my God, Iron!
I just said it's over!
Show some restraint.
[sighs]
Don't make me regret you.
[thumping]
[roars]
[footfall]
[PARK HEEJIN]
We're safe now, aren't we?
Yeah.
[sighing]
[SUNG JINWOO]
We should get going.
[gasps]
[crackling]
Our gate's waiting.
[chuckle]
Yeah!
We're really leaving
this place and going home!
[HAN SONG-YI]
I was holding my breath!
[GO MYUNGHWAN]
I think we all were!
[PARK HEEJIN]
Well, we can breathe now!
[SUNG JINWOO]
Before I go...
[AHN SANGMIN] At this point,
I would estimate that
a week has passed
inside the gate.
President, why don't you
go on home and rest?
Kichul and I can wait here.
With our guild members
trapped inside...
I'll stay right where I am.
-[sighs]
-At least till morning breaks.
[gasping]
[AHN SANGMIN] Look...
they're coming out!
-[chuckles]
-[BAEK YOONHO] Nice job, Kim!
[BAEK YOONHO]
If anyone could pull through,
of course it'd be you!
President Baek's here!
[BAEK YOONHO]
Hunter Park.
Hunter Go.
I'm glad to see
you're both alive and well.
But what about the others?
[gasps]
[footfall]
♪
Hunter Sung's back!
Yes!
[AHN SANGMIN]
I totally called it!
[crackling]
It closed.
That's all?
[BAEK YOONHO]
No one else?
Not even Kim?
[PARK HEEJIN]
Mm-hm.
♪
[BAEK YOONHO] Except for Park,
you're all lower ranks.
So, what went on in there?
[SUNG JINWOO] Let's go,
I'll drive you home.
[HAN SONG-YI]
Oh, um, cool.
Hang on a second.
I have questions and you're
going to answer them for me.
[SUNG JINWOO]
No thank you,
save them for someone
from your guild.
I'm tired.
[groans]
[BAEK YOONHO]
I wasn't making a suggestion,
I was giving an order.
Perhaps you're not aware,
but I lead this guild,
and six of our members
are now gone.
As their president,
it falls on me
to find out what happened.
♪
While that might be true,
I'm the reason your surviving
tigers even lived.
As their president...
shouldn't you show me
the proper gratitude?
♪
[BAEK YOONHO]
Please, excuse me.
You're absolutely right.
I'm sorry for getting
carried away.
[engine whirring]
[BAEK YOONHO] Hunter Park.
[PARK HEEJIN] Yes, sir?
Who in the world was that?
Doesn't seem like he's looking
to make any friends.
Guess not.
[PARK HEEJIN]
After he beat the boss,
his mood turned sour
all of a sudden.
[AHN SANGMIN]
Well, yeah.
Who isn't crabby
when they're dog-tired?
Doesn't make him a bad guy.
[sighs]
Get to work, Ahn.
You have got to recruit him.
I want that hunter
in our guild,
whatever it takes.
Oh, sure!
[sighs]
[AHN SANGMIN] Looks like
I was right about
Jinwoo Sung all along.
[car engine idling]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Good night.
Get home safe.
-Hm.
-[sighs]
[HAN SONG-YI]
Um, Jinwoo?
Hm?
Not "Mister?"
Thanks for today
and all the days in the gate.
And, um, just so you know,
I'm going to be counting
on you next time.
[footfall]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Okay.
I forgot.
Only a few hours passed
here in our world.
[sword clanking]
I didn't walk away completely
empty-handed, but...
Nothing I could do if my level
wasn't high enough.
[wind gusting]
[sighs]
Damn it!
I doubt a fourth attempt
would've helped.
A lot of effort
for almost no gain.
[water trickling]
Almost...
♪
I guess.
That makes three times.
[water trickling]
[SUNG JINAH]
Hurry up, Jinwoo.
I'm gonna eat without you!
Yeah, I'll be right there.
♪
[YOO JINHO]
Top of the morning, boss!
[SUNG JINWOO]
You're seriously wearing that?
It's lit!
Now let's head out!
[chuckles]
Oh, and, um...
there's someone
we gotta pick up on the way.
[YOO JINHO]
Who?
[car door opens]
Morning, Captain Yoo!
You good?
Uh, yeah, I'm great.
[chuckles]
Thanks for the lift... Jinwoo.
[YOO JINHO]
Not "Mister?"
Did you get
any sleep last night?
Are you kidding?
Not even a little!
Yeah, I guess I did
get you home pretty late.
It's okay.
[YOO JINHO] She got home late,
and didn't sleep?
By the way, Jinwoo...
[YOO JINHO]
I get what it means,
b-but I don't want to!
Take a nap,
I can wake you up.
-[YOO JINHO] H-hey, uh, Boss?
-I actually think I might...
Hm?
Miss Han is underage.
You do know that, right?
[groans]
What about it?
[gasps]
[trembling]
[YOO JINHO]
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
[car engine revving]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Let's wrap these raids up fast.
[HAN SONG-YI]
You got it, Jinwoo!
[YOO JINHO]
Uh, huh.
♪